{
    "section1":"Section 1:Demo for post/get Json data through RESTFUL API",
    "section2":"Section 2:Demo for loading data through RESTFUL API",
    "section3":"Section 3:Demo for keeping same session through cookies",
    "section4":"Section 4:Demo for CORS",
    "section5":"Section 5:Demo for layout for Mobile",
    "profiles": [
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Mike",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Claudio",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Ben",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Atul",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Russell",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Francis",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Tim",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Shiv",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Gabriela Perez",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"

        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Tracy",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Name",
            "Answer": "Maria Lindsay Hipolito",
            "UserID": 23456,
            "ClientID": 65432,
            "Email": "abc@.toronto.ca",
            "Phone": "4164445656",
            "postcode":"M2G4E3"
        }
    ]
}